理解合同中有关的部分
To understand the part of the contract related
对于hashcode方法，我们需要了解hash
to the hashcode method, we need to have some idea of how hash
表可以工作，因为有两个非常常见的集合
tables work , because two very common collection
在Java库HashSet和HashMap中的实现
implementations in the Java library HashSet and HashMap
两者都在内部使用哈希表数据结构。
both use a hash table data structure inside.
它们依赖于对象的hashcode
And they depend on the hashcode for the objects that
分别存储在集合中或用作映射中的键。
are stored in the set or used as keys in the map respectively.
所以哈希表是映射的表示。
So a hash table is a representation of a mapping.
它是一种将键映射到值的抽象数据类型。
It's an abstract data type that maps keys to values.
哈希表提供恒定的时间查找。
Hash tables offer constant time look up.
所以他们往往比树或列表表现得更好
So they tend to perform better than trees or lists
当用于映射时。
when used for a mapping.
哈希映射中的键不必排序，甚至
The keys in a hash map don't have to be ordered, even
拥有任何特定的财产，除了
to have any particular property, except for offering equals
还有哈希码。
and hashcode.
下面是哈希表的工作原理。
And here's how a hash table works.
所以它包含一个初始化为边大小的数组
So it contains an array that's initialized to a side size
对应于元素的数量
corresponding to the number of elements
我们希望最终出现在哈希集中。
that we expect to eventually appear in the HashSet.
不过，这可能会增长和缩小。
This can grow and shrink, though.
当某个值中有一个键表示要插入时，
When a key in a value represented for insertion,
我们计算密钥的哈希码
we compute the hashcode of the key
并将其转换为数组范围内的索引，
and convert it into an index in the array's range,
通常由一些模块划分。
usually by some modular division.
然后在索引处插入值。
And then the value is inserted at that index.
散列表的rep不变量
The rep invariant of a hash table
包含此基本约束
includes this fundamental constraint
密钥存储在确定的插槽中
that keys are stored in the slots determined
他们的散列码。
by their hash codes.
现在哈希码的设计使得密钥
Now hash codes are designed so that the keys will be
在指数上均匀分布。
spread evenly over the indices.
但偶尔会发生冲突
But occasionally a conflict occurs, and two keys
以相同的指数结束。
end up at the same index.
所以，与其在一个指数中只保持一个值，
So rather than holding at just a single value in an index,
哈希表实际上包含一个键值对列表，
a hash table actually holds a list of key value pairs,
通常称为散列桶。
usually called a hash bucket.
用Java实现的键-值对，通常
Key value pairs implemented in Java, typically, simply
是具有两个字段的对象。
is an object with two fields.
插入时，向数组槽中的列表中添加一对
On insertion, you add a pair to the list in the array slot
由哈希码决定。
determined by the hashcode.
查一下，你把钥匙散开，找到合适的位置，
For look up, you hash the key, find the right slot,
然后检查每一对，
and then examine each of the pairs,
直到找到与查询键相等的键。
until one has found whose key equals the query key.
所以现在应该清楚为什么目标承包商需要
So now it should be clear why the object contractor requires
具有相同哈希代码的相等对象。
equal objects to have the same hashcode.
如果两个相等的对象有不同的散列码，
If two equal objects had distinct hash codes,
它们可能被放在不同的位置。
they might be placed in different slots.
所以如果你倾向于使用
So if you tend to look up a value using
一把相当于插入的钥匙，
a key equal to the one with which it was inserted,
查找可能会失败。
the look-up might fail.
对象默认具有良好的实现是一致的
Objects default has good implementation is consistent
默认等于。
with it's default equals.
所以记住它是默认的等于。
So remember that it's default equals.
这是指代平等。
That's referential equality.
默认的hashcode实际上返回一个整数，基本上，
It's default hashcode actually returns an integer, basically,
从存储器中表示或计算的
representing or computed from the memory
对象的地址。
address of the object.
所以对于参考文献a和b，如果a等于
So for references a and b, if a equals equals
b、 那么a的地址必须等于b的地址。
b, then the address of a has to equal equal the address of b.
所以标的合同确实得到了满足。
So the object contract is indeed satisfied.
但是不可变的对象需要不同的实现
But immutable objects need a different implementation
因为它们重写了这个equals方法。
of hashcode, because they override this equals method.
现在是持续时间，因为我们还没有覆盖默认值
Now for durations, since we haven't overridden the default
hashcode现在，我们正在破坏
hashcode yet, we're actually currently breaking
目标合同。
the object contract.
我们可以制作两个不同的持续时间对象。
We can make two different duration objects.
但是如果他们有相同的时间，那么
But if they have the same minutes and seconds, then
我们的平等，我们被超越的平等，
our equals, our overridden equals,
将它们比较为相等，但有哈希码
will compare them as equal, but there hashcodes
可能大不相同。
may be wildly different.
所以我们需要解决这个问题。
So we need to fix that.
现在一个简单而激烈的方法来确保合同得到履行
Now a simple and drastic way to ensure the contract is met
hashcode总是返回相同的常量值
is for hashcode to always return the same constant value
所以每个对象的hashcode，每个duration对象的
so that every object's hashcode, every duration object's
例如，hashcode是相同的。
hashcode, for example, is the same.
这符合目标合同，
This satisfies the object contract,
但这会带来灾难性的业绩影响，
but it would have a disastrous performance effect,
因为每一个密钥最终都会存储在同一个插槽中。
since every key would end up being stored in the same slot.
假设我们选择了整数761，
Let's say, we chose the integer 761,
哈希表的所有键都在那个槽中。
all the keys of the hash table would be in that slot.
它的性能会退化
And its performance would degenerate
只是一个长列表的线性搜索
to just that of a linear search along a long list
在那个散列槽里。
in that hash slot.
以及构造更合理的哈希代码的标准方法
And a standard way to construct a more reasonable hashcode that
仍然满足契约是计算哈希码
still satisfies the contract is to compute a hashcode
对于对象的每个组件
for each component of the object that's
用于质量的终止——例如，这里，
used in the termination of the quality-- for example, here,
我们用持续时间内的秒数--
we're using the seconds in the duration--
然后把这些结合起来，再加上一些算法
and then combining these, throwing in a few arithmetic
操作。
operations.
在持续时间内，这很容易。
For duration, this is easy.
类的抽象值已经是整数值，
The abstract value of the class is already an integer value,
获取长度和秒数。
get length and seconds.
所以我们可以把它作为hashcode返回。
So we can actually just return that, as our hashcode.
现在有一本很棒的书
Now there's a fantastic book written
作者Josh Bloch称之为有效Java
by Josh Bloch called Effective Java-- that I highly
推荐——这就更详细地解释了这个问题
recommend-- that explains this issue in more detail
并给出了一些编写适当哈希代码的策略
and gives some strategies for writing decent hashcode
功能。
functions.
他的建议已经在一本好书中总结了
And his advice has been summarized in a good Slashdot
我也会鼓励你阅读。
post that I would also encourage you to read.
但是Java的最新版本，现在，实际上
But recent versions of Java, now, actually
有一个实用方法，对象的散列，
have a utility method, object's hash,
这使得实现包含
that makes it easier to implement hashcode involving
多个字段。
multiple fields.
所以你可以在Java库中查找。
So you can look that up in the Java library.
不过，请注意，只要您满足要求
Note, however, that as long as you satisfy the requirement
相同的对象具有相同的hashcode值，
that equal objects have the same hashcode value,
然后使用特定的散列技术
then the particular hashing technique you use
不会影响代码的正确性。
doesn't make a difference to the correctness of your code.
它可能通过创建
It may affect its performance by creating
不同物体之间不必要的碰撞，
these unnecessary collisions between different objects,
但即使是性能很差的散列函数
but even a poorly performing hash function
总比坏了的好，
is better than one that is broken,
那违反了合同。
that breaks the contract.
最重要的是，如果不重写hashcode
Most crucially notice that if you don't override hashcode
总之，您将得到一个来自对象的，它基于
at all, you'll get a one from object, which is based
在对象的地址上。
on the address of the object.
所以如果你重写了equals，
So if you have overridden equals,
这意味着你几乎肯定违反了
this will mean that you have almost certainly violated
合同。
the contract.
所以一般来说，总是重写hashcode
So as a general rule, always override hashcode
当你覆盖等于时。
when you override equals.
现在搞糟这件事的一个方法是拼错哈希码。
Now one way to mess this up is to misspell hashcode.
很多年前麻省理工学院的一个学生，
Many years ago a student in this class, at MIT,
花了几个小时追踪一个项目中的错误
spent hours tracking down a bug in a project that
只不过是拼错了哈希码
amounted nothing more than misspelling hashcode
作为hashcode小写c。
as hashcode lowercase c.
这创造了一种新的方法
This created a new method, as we've
在前面的阅读中看到。
seen earlier in this reading.
它是用等号创建的。
It was created with equals.
这创建了一个没有重写的新方法
This created a new method that didn't override
对象的hashcode方法和奇怪的东西
the hashcode method of object at all and strange things
发生了。
happened.
就像我们为平等而做的一样，永远
So just like we did for equals, always
对hashcode也使用该重写。
use that override for hashcode as well.